ZAKARIA ABID

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

Phone: +212706080306

E-mail : zakariaabid509@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/zakaria2abid Adresse : Lot Agdal , N° 47 ,

Étage 2 Bouznika . (+212) 7 06 08 03 06

Portfolio: ziko442.github.io/MyPortfolio

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

Coursera Platform: Complete the Django for Everybody specialization, commissioned by the University of Michigan

Link:

course ra. or g/verify/specialization/TXRMQC4ZVQBF

Coursera Platform: Complete the Python for Everybody specialization, commissioned by the University of Michigan.

Link:

course ra. org/verify/specialization/475 QDEA7NNE5

ABOUT ME

Certified full stack developer, with 2 years of experience. I learned to code from an early age in various computer languages (Javascript, Java, Angular...) and created personal projects. Versatile, I master the different technical stages of creating a web application from understanding user needs to frontend and backend development and maintenance.

WORK HISTORY

Experiences and Projects

Full Stack Web Developer (Trainee)

- On LIBENS CONSULTING, this internship, lasting six months, internship 06/2020 to 01/2021, I fulfilled the objectives of my internship with java and angular technology

Full-Stack Developer

- On BRATIL CONSULTING 02/2021 to 05/2021, dotnet and angular technologies, report generator project work to automate the work of writing the control office report

E-Commerce web app : BookStore (java)

E-commerce application which aims to display a list of books for sale, with dynamic and interactive interfaces, as well as

pages that allow the registration of customers and the addition of selected products to the basket.

Link: https://github.com/ziko442/BookStore

Micro web app: student-tracker (j2ee)

CRUD based web application using MVC based student tracking software - Java, JSP, Servlets, JDBC, MySQL database, MySQL Workbench.

link: https://github.com/ziko442/student-tracker

EDUCATION

Faculty of Sciences Ain Chock (FSAC)

Professional License in JEE and DOTNET Development, 2018 to 2019

TSDI

Specialized Technician Diploma in IT Development, 2017 to 2018

SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Web & Design:

- Angular framework CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Architecture en J2EE et Développement d'applications J2EE(JSP, SERVLET, MVC) APIs - "Application Programming Interfaces".
- DOM, NPM Adobe XD, sketch Language and Technique:
- spring: spring framework 5 & spring boot.
- CRUD Operations, Maven, Hibernate, JPA.
- Git, Github et contrôle de version et Agile/Jira
- Maîtrise des langages : JAVA , UML , POO, Python, C/C++, dotnet
- Base des données : SQL (TS SQL,MySQL,PL/SQL,MS SQL Server)

Unix/linux et command line